foreign
all right guys so welcome back to
another video so in this video we got
Adrian one of my top students he just
had a 10 000 day and like I've been kind
of like challenging him lately because
he's like one of the most active guys in
my chat and he's like he's had a thing
on his own without my trades like five
six week winning streak when I got it
bro if you have a big day which he just
had his ten thousand dollar day I'm
gonna let you drive my Lambo I'm just
gonna give it to him right but I'm here
at Best Buy right now because if we get
back home safe if he doesn't mess up my
Lambo crash or anything I'm gonna give
him two brand new monitors and I know
the setup he has right now isn't the
craziest so if we get back home safe and
we gave him the two monitors
if he messes up the lambo the monitor's
out for grabs so drop a comment you know
hopefully we get back safe in the lambo
um we're gonna go to Starbucks and let's
see where the video takes us let's go
[Music]
so we didn't think this through
we're gonna have to call for back
so the top student just pulled up to the
building
um so it's Halloween so I have a little
surprise for him we're gonna go pick him
up right now take him upstairs and then
we're gonna give him the keys to the
lambo so we go for a ride let's pull up
yeah
okay so this is my top student bro how
old are you 17 2017 now 17 and then you
dropped out of high school right yeah
I'm doing an online school right now all
right yeah so I mean something that like
he was like I was telling him like bro
like you know you dropped that high so
you have all the free time in the world
like you're in like a position right now
where like if you do this right like you
can literally be good for life like you
don't have to go College school like
you're literally good so it's not as big
as 10 000 a day um we're gonna go
upstairs I have another surprise for him
we'll have two surprises for him you
guys already saw the first surprise that
was gonna be the second one and um we're
gonna take him to go drive the lambo so
please take care
all right let's go
foreign
agent around kind of like the office for
like I did you know did the podcast
um where like kind of the magic happens
to me and him are always like on zooms
back and forth so I'll just showing them
in the space but um you have a Halloween
costumes
all right we're gonna give him the uh FX
Alex G Trader starter pack watch stay
tuned
thank you
I have Alex
but I actually missing you're missing
one thing though yeah let's go make some
cake pops let's go
foreign how does it feel to be like part
of the video like in front of the camera
like how does it feel but it actually
it's really crazy like from going from
watching the videos to now like actually
like being a part of it it's actually
really crazy like motivational that's
fine I mean just don't don't get nervous
and you'll be good so let's go get some
cake pops
[Music]
all right so now we're on our way to uh
Starbucks like I'm kind of giving him
like you know how to it's your first
time in a Lambo or no yeah
it's just crazy different
boys I mean he's bringing a lot of
people think like you got mad like
compared to the McLaren the McLaren is
smaller
[Music]
foreign
like bro the results that you're like
making like I'm showing you this
lifestyle because like bro you're close
to it like it's a little bit more
consistency so I'm done doing boot camp
so kind of like this next clip is what I
have next
in the past two months I've been feeling
down knowing I've been letting my whole
entire Community down after doing the
video with Josh the guy that I picked up
from McDonald's you know as I'm reading
through the comments I'm realizing I've
never dropped beginner gems ever these
are things I have never exposed for the
past four years I've only worked with 80
selected students to be part of my boot
camp leaving many out there to not have
the proper education to succeed in this
industry I apologize I take full
responsibility because I've been
building my own room for you guys so I
can leave a legacy for all of those very
well-deserved and dedicated Traders but
now the time has come to where
everything that has given me the
opportunity to have six figure weeks
have 14 week winning streaks the skill
set that I have never shown and only
given access to 80 lucky selected
students has now been combined on the
what's Housewives of Forex Trading along
with my sacred trading strategy and my
golden trading plan that I have fully
finally perfected after four long years
it will now be showcased on a guided
boot camp with all of the live
recordings from boot camp one all the
way to boot camp 4 showing the growth of
the students that were part of it and
what awaits you inside all and also I'm
going to be doing a weekly webinar with
the private Community once you join the
seven figure Army so I make sure I never
let you guys down ever again because
once you're part of the center forget
family that's for life
yo Adrian
you also tell me how did you meet Alex
okay so the way I'm Alex I went to the
city place one night and I saw his car
there on the garage like in the garage
and I saw his sticker he's had an
Instagram on it I was like damn I want
to see what he does and then I just
searched him up on on Instagram and so
he was unfortunate and that's how that's
how I learned yo and since you're so
young how long have you been trading
I've actually been trading for like
around six and a half months now yeah
probably around six months and in what
way has the book kind of talked to you
bro just if it wasn't for the boot camp
I wouldn't be where I'm at today like
it's just changed my training mode
oh my God you understood
yeah worry about it we're about to wrap
up oh I mean I have could you guys know
what I said at the beginning we got back
home safe right so first of all I
appreciate you for getting us home safe
in the car get it you didn't mess it up
I appreciate you bro helping me out like
in all the chats like you know like you
moderate all the chats and stuff so I
want to make sure like you elevated your
trading right so you gotta like see the
trading better I got something
I got like the two biggest monitors that
I can find this is all for you bro so
congratulations
I know um you can't take this in the
lambo trust me they don't fit you can
pop up a picture right now like they're
not even afraid of the truck so this is
all for you bro
all right so obviously he didn't [__] up
the Lamb of salt he's taking these home
today so bro I appreciate you for real
for doing it
um so make sure to like comment
subscribe um if you guys want to be part
of the guided boot camp the launch is on
11 11 2022. if you guys are watching
this in the future you guys Mitch uh
missed the launch date like it is closed
like after 11 11 it will be closed until
next year two three months so I don't
really like giving access
um to my you know secrets and trading
very often like I only do it with
selected people so make sure to be part
of the launch on 11 11 and if you don't
you know get that uh you're not part of
the launch just make sure you know
follow me Instagram or subscribe so you
stay tuned to the next one so now we're
gonna go and I'm gonna show you guys a
little uh quick chart breakdown on the
tray that I could have made easily 20
30k so stay tuned
foreign
[Music]
you know it was a mix of events
obviously we plan to go get the k-pops
after the cake pops we are going to come
back to the house do the chart breakdown
but then we got the post that you know
naok was going to be there so we pulled
up first of all I want to appreciate you
Adrian you know I've already told you a
bunch of times but when I'm not active
in the Discord and I'm not able to you
know go out there and reply to all of
the students that need help with
questions he's always helped me out
jumps in and have some more any
questions he does zooms with all of the
students every single time so for those
of you guys that joined the guided boot
camp are you guys guys are going to see
Adrian very often he's always doing
zooms when I'm not so you know we're
always interacting with the community
but today I want to show you guys this
super simple trade I could have easily
made 10 20 30 40 50k on if I would have
obviously put the right lot size but I
ended up just getting Wicked out by a
single of a pip it literally had my
entry perfectly to my take profit
perfectly right so this is going to be
USD card
you guys can go check out the ground
like I posted this all over my Instagram
so we're going to start off with you can
see how the daily was bullish at one
point then obviously here we shifted to
bearish after we went bearish we went
bullish again creating higher low and
higher high as you can tell at this
point we are using the same level that
was once used as resistance then use
that support then use that support so
use that support again the moment we
body closed under this point I'm waiting
for a retracement so it uses it as
resistance obviously whenever we're
under this level we're selling whenever
we're above we're buying right there's a
very simple concept support and
resistance it should not get any more
complicated than this supply and demand
this it's all the same thing obviously
you want to call it whatever you want I
call it support and resistance keep it
simple there's no need to complicate it
it's like calling a steering wheel a
driver
maneuvering steering no it's a steering
wheel people it's you don't have to go
all crazy to the support of resistance
so after the daily time frame
um so I'd say in this case right here
when we broke under this level of
support support we identify that we need
a retracement in order to sell so this
is where I would go down to the four
hour what a coincidence on the four hour
you could even see it in more detail how
it is such a stronger level of support
here one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten like look at all these
times this level is respected and every
single time we're above we're buying
every single time we're under we're
selling above buying Under selling so in
this case we're under so what are we
trying to do so like you're not trying
to buy into this area so that's where we
would wait for the retracement into this
level once you get the retracement at
this level this is where I start
building up my confluences so here we'll
have rejection from daily area of
Interest rejection from previous four
hour structure rejection from EMA
rejection maybe from a psychological
level
um and now we will be waiting for kind
of like our entry signal our rejection
candlesticks so this is great this is
actually very good this is where I would
be answering because you could have a
four hour doji rejection you would take
this kind of put your stop loss above
however you want to modify your stop
loss and then when it comes to my take
profit I'm going to place it at the next
daily structure point so this would be
the next daily support level where we
would take this uh we will be looking to
get out of this trade and you can see
how it is almost stairs to the upside
and then it is stairs now about to
switch to the downside you guys can see
that very clearly there and pretty
self-explanatory after that the trade
pretty much goes all the way to take
profit if you didn't manage to get entry
on this first trade comes back gives you
another rejection candle again a
rejection from the EMA rejection from
structure like so much that this trade
gave me confidence to take it I did take
it around here and then I had my stop
loss around here literally waking us out
by a Pip this would have been easy I
think I had it marked up out of one to
five so maybe this was around like this
so we had a 40 pip stop loss for 100 for
a 200 pip take profit worked this up by
a pip I don't change my trading strategy
I don't change my trading approach I
don't do anything whenever this happens
I simply move on to the next trade let's
say you were going to go catch a bus for
whatever case and you missed the bus you
simply wait for another bus you're not
gonna now change your route and go
somewhere else no it's the same thing
same destination you just gotta wait on
another bus so we're trying to do the
same thing trying to catch the same
trades with the same probabilities we
missed it we just catch another trade so
this one kind of sucked because we lost
so we didn't kind of miss it but you
know wake this out and I'm not here to
so you guys a dream that they're always
all perfect the strategy is
and you can get these trades endlessly
and um it's a perfect example of a
beautiful trade I would have gotten uh
but yeah I do these breakdowns a lot of
times with the students with the signals
so if you guys want to know more
information about all that stuff the
link is in the description below make
sure to like comment and subscribe I do
these videos very often privately
um not so much here on YouTube because
everybody does it here on YouTube it's
almost kind of boring everybody's doing
the same thing every single time so I
like doing things um very differently so
yeah try breakdowns always in the in the
Discord in the telegram and again when
you're going to trade keep it simple
Mark get structure and it can be as
simple as buying at a level of
resistance use that support to go to the
upside and then if you shift to the
downside now use the same exact level
that was used as resistance and support
to now sell from this level to go to the
downside so hope you guys found this
video useful if you guys want to see
more chart breakdowns or more more in
detail this is something obviously very
brief make sure to drop a comment and I
will make sure to read it so see you
guys in the next video